<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShweOh</string>
    <string name="LOGIN">Login</string>
    <string name="PASSWORD">Password</string>
    <string name="USERNAME">Username</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="nav_item_home">HOME</string>
    <string name="nav_item_friends">FRIEND</string>
    <string name="nav_item_notifications">NOTIFICATIONS</string>
    <string name="ham_english">English</string>
    <string name="ham_burmese">Burmese</string>
    <string name="ham_package">Package</string>

    <string-array name="nav_drawer_labels">
        <item>@string/nav_item_home</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_friends</item>
        <item>@string/nav_item_notifications</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="about_instructor">    Hi, I\'m James. I have a degree in computing from Imperial College London, and a physics diploma from the Open University.I started working for myself at the age of 15, and never looked back. I explored careers as varied as being a commercial pilot, stunt-man, rock climbing instructor, and more. None of these provided a continued challenge, and stable income in the same way technology does.</string>
    <string name="seeMore_aboutInstructor">After building and selling a home computer support business, I became an angel investor and business mentor here in Cambridge UK. I fell in love with teaching game development through one of my investments, and I now spend all of my time sharing my passion with people like you.</string>
    <string name="android_course">Create Professional Java Applications \n

Create Greate Android Applications \n

Apply for your dream job as an Android Developer \n

Bring your own App Idea to Life \n

Build a fantastic resume in order to show to employers \n

Master Java Programming Language \n
</string>

    <string name="about_course">Basic Concepts of Programming \n

Java Programming Basics \n

Intermediate and Advanced Java Programming - Learn Java by Building Android Apps \n

Intermediate Java Programming - Learn Java by Creating Android Apps! \n

Advanced Java programing - Learn Java by Creating Android Apps! \n

Android Programming \n

Android Programming Basics \n

Intermediate and Advanced Android Programming \n

Firebase as Backend for Android Apps! \n

Source Codes \n

Create Complex Android Apps - Production Ready Apps! \n
</string>
</resources>
